Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/vaishali-sankale-8a816845 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

java 8

java 7

Java

Certifications

Oracle Certified Java professional
Agile Professional Certificate
Credit Card Banker Certificate from
IIBF

IBM Datacap taskmaster capture 8.1 professional

vaishali sankale

Senior Java Developer at Crédit Agricole CIB Singapore

Summary

Experienced Senior Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the Banking/Payment and information technology services industry. Skilled in API,WebServices ,Spring boot,Spring framework ,Core java ,J2EE, SQL, Oracle Database,Kafka, docker, Document Management, and Agile Methodologies . Also have working knowledge on bigdata technology stack like spark ,no sql databases HBASE. Engineering professional graduated from IET DAVV indore.

Experience

Crédit Agricole CIB Senior Java Developer May 2018 - Present (2 years 11 months) Singapore

Accenture
Senior Software Developer
August 2014 - March 2018 (3 years 8 months)
Mumbai Area, India

Cap Gemini Software Engineer November 2011 - August 2014 (2 years 10 months) Mumbai Area, India

Education

Chrisitian Eminent Higher Secondary School (2005 - 2007)

Devi Ahilya Vishwavidyalaya Bachelor of Engineering (BEng), Information Technology · (2011)